

Contact Info



(○) **(**3)+375 **(**29) 664-80-22



MINSK, BELARUS



bobrgord76@gmail.com



Portfolio



in <u>linkedin</u>



<u>GitHub</u>



Codewars

Skills

- REACT/REDUX
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- AXIOS/REST API
- TDD/Unit Tests
- StoryBook/snapshot
- Material UI
- Git/GitHub
- Postman
- 3Dmax

Languages

- English A2(in progress)
- Belarusian advanced
- Russian proficiency

SERGEY GORDEENKO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT/REDUX)

About me

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming. I have experience in creating SPA with React, Redux, TypeScript.

Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. I'm planning to study Node.js, because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. I spend my leisure time on Codewars, improve my English and skills developer. Open for your suggestions.

My PROJECTS

PART TIME (END OF 2021 - PRESENT)

Link to GitHub Cards

Stack: Next.js, TypeScript, React, Redux Toolkit, Redux-Thunk, Axios, REST API, React Hook Form, React Query, Team development, Bug fixing, deploying.

Social Network **Link to GitHub**

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React-Routerdom, Axios, REST API, Bug fixing, deploying.

Link to GitHub Todolist

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux Toolkit, Redux-thunk, Routerdom, Axios, REST API, Mui, Formik, Storybook; Bug fixing, deploying.

Link to GitHub MoGo

Stack: HTML, CSS.

Work Experience

2021-2022 - Took part in creating learning app, developed login page, modal windows, tests, menu and design. Use next developer technologies: React/Redux, ReduxThunk, RestApi, Axios, ReduxForm, Formik, MaterialUI, SCSS, etc. Check the correctness of the code with Unit Tests and take Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application. Use TypeScript for best control of the code in work.

2015-2021 - Deputy director Advertisement studio 'Ricco-Graphic'.

Execution and maintenance of contracts and various types of agreements. Communication with suppliers and customers. Control of deadlines for fulfilling orders.

Management of financial, economic activities of the enterprise. Conducting staff assessment and training. Optimization of the organizational structure of the enterprise and reducing the cost of production. Management of production, control of personnel records management, interviewing.

Education

2021-2022 - IT-INCUBATOR

React/Redux, JS/TypeScript, front-end developer Test/StoryBook, AXIOS/REST API, Git, Material UI/Ant Desing, HTML5/CSS3

2020-2021 - EDUCATIONAL CENTER 'V TOPE'

contextual development, SEO&SMM promotion, advertising, content marketing

2021 - BELHARD ACADEMY

modern Front-End with JS and HTML5, website development

1999 - MILITARY ACADEMY OF THE BELARUS. Radio engineer